Hello friends, I welcome you
to my YouTube channel.
In this video, I'm going to tell you
about Flipkart Coronavirus Insurance. Friends, Flipkart Coronavirus
Instant, which has recently been launched in Mai Ke Mandir,
friends, and this offer
is available for one year. Friends,
its validity will be for one year. How
can you get this insurance?
First of all, you have to come here
in the Flipkart application. Here in the shop option,
you have to leave it and look downwards.
Friends, here you will see
Flipkart Insurance. Simply
click on it. Friends, here
you will see friends, life
insurance with comedy night in power.
Friends, this is new recently. Friends, it was
launched around 28 May in the month of May.
Friends, there are four plans here. Friends,
basically the first one gives a cover of 15 lakhs, the second one gives a cover of 10 lakhs, the
second one gives a cover of 10 lakhs,
and a separate quote
gives a cover of 40 lakhs. Friends, and
in this, the first one is a plan. Friends,
that 903 plan is suitable.  It is within 1000, the
second is 1805 which is within 2,000, the
third is friends which is 3737 which is
within 4000 and the fourth plan is 5600 and 591
friends which is within 6000,
friends here you have to directly click on the
plan option, you have seen that there are
only four plans in it friends
and in one you get 50,000, like
you get treatment in Vinya,
friends, you know the reason for this
and in the remaining three you get one lakh rupees,
friends, if you get
infection rate in fact from Corona balance, then
friends, you will see here at the bottom,
click on the date and time in condition, friends,
you can see its time number below, so this is
for the group of 18 years to 50 years, friends, that is, those
below 18 years cannot take it, and those
above 50 years cannot take
it, like while purchasing insurance,
its policy is for one year  Friends and this
is our Nandi Ji Anmol friends, it means you
cannot increase the policy again, so
in this you can take one on a fake account,
friends you can see this here
which is of Ajwain, here is its
insurance friends, its email ID and
customer care number, friends you can see the
group on the screen and it is Radhe-Radhe Gyan
live.com friends and its customer care
number is one 0 you will see on the screen friends
and this is old now as you know there
is no renewal friends and here
you can also see health depression here as
you should not have cancer disease in this, there should
not be heart disease, there should not be
heart attack and
stroke disease, there should not be
diplegia, you should not have any
disease of diabetes, you should
not have any kind of blood pressure disease in this,
chest or hot boobs and
friends of this, you have got its operation or later
operation in the feature, it seems from now on that
you have to get the operation done in the feature, you should
not have all these diseases, there should
not be any discharge of liver and
kidney failure  You should
not have paralysis, so you should
not have any kind of nervous disorder, you should
not have any neurological disorder,
you should not have any infection, you should
not have AIDS disease, there should
not be any disability, friends, wind
spine or bonds, friends and for the last two years, that is,
friends, today is 9th June, friends
and for the last two years, that is, before 9th June 2018,
if you should not have any kind of disease, such that you are
continuously
admitted in the hospital, have
returned your honor, former area, you should not have all these diseases
in the last two years, only then
this policy is valid, otherwise even if you
buy it, if they come to know about it, then
this policy itself is not valid, if you face any
problem in making any payment, then
you will not get it, friends, it has been
told to you directly in this and
it has been told friends, you should not have been in any country outside India for 45 days before,
say June and only 45 days before,
friends, this is it and for such
cases, there is a waiting period,
friends, if you buy the non-  It should be on a 14 day
meeting, you will have it from the 15th day itself, which will be for
24 days, even if you get the
design factor of immediate refund, then also the
account will not be opened, friends, suppose you are
buying the plan here today,
its insurance, whatever you call it, even
before that you
should not have any quick treatment for the rain, friends, even if there is an
exit point, then also you will
not get the insurance bill added, friends, now let's
talk about these four plans, friends, the
first one is on 903, in which you will get 50 thousand
rupees directly, friends, which will
come in your account, if you do your test
in the treatment of the plan for 24 hours, which will be a
government recognized
center, that is, government authorized,
then you will go and this direct
or word of promotion will be transferred to your account,
friends, which you can see, you should
remain in the menu for 24 hours and now
show its liability there, 1850 rain 30 days, there
is translation in it, friends, if you buy the policy today, then
within 30 days
You cannot cancel it inside, it has become
valid, you can also click on tax in it,
which you must be seeing
under section 80C and after the second life,
you have done it which is of 28 and ₹500,
friends, there is death insurance of 10 lakhs in it,
friends, if you have a tax
and it becomes current, when you like,
after that friends,
after the coronavirus statement is done in the government lab,
then you get 10 lakhs in the name of your nominee, in this, there are people between
18 to 50 years of age, there has been a
30-day cancellation and there
is a validity of 1 year, in this you can claim tax
under section 80C,
friends, and let me talk about it, it is of
Rs 203 or 737 of the old, friends, let's
talk about it now, there is a death insurance of 25 lakhs in
it, so see, if
you die under unclaimed treatment, then 225
lakh rupees will go to your Navami account,
friends, here you will get instant benefit of 1 lakh
But you will get votes friends, see this, if
you have taken such insurance then the thread is returned, which
you get tested in the authorized center, it is
taken out there, 24 hours are completed,
then you will get one lakh rupees here,
friends, the termination should be removed, the person should be
healthy, you
can cancel this policy within 30 days, this policy has a
validity of one year, you
can click inside ATC and talk about it,
which is a small last plan, friends, on 5600 and
59, in this you will get a date of 40 lakh rupees, you
will see that in your job you will get
40 lakh rupees in your account and you will get 1 lakh rupees in it
instantly, friends, this is a possible suggestion,
24 hours due to coronavirus history, whether
it is government or private, which is a
closed loop, in that you should be
within 50 years of age, the cancellation policy of 38 days, which
was in the remaining days, in this also there is a balance of one year, which is in the
remaining  In the day, it is the same in this also and
in this you get it for tax
inside Shikshan BTC, friends how
can you bike, then it does
not require medical proof at the time of purchase
but when you go to claim it,
you need medical proof
and it should also be physical, friends only
then you get it in it,
no one takes GST from you in this, there is internal inclusion in the test separately,
friends
you can see here in this I will be showing you
customer care helpline number and
email ID, friends, so you directly boil,
like in case you fry this
903 pack, this is fine friends and here
you click on the continue option,
friends as you
click on the continue option, friends, you will be
asked for your name there, address will be asked,
phone number will be asked, friends here
you have to first click on the turmeric condition,
like you have never gone out of India for
45 days before buying this police,
so yes friends Ajay,
you are having fever at the time of buying, Pranav
and you are feeling its sensation, friends even then
You should not buy Islam in 14 days,
see this cough is like this, so two Ajay Dev,
problems in relationships, two
quarantine, you from this, before taking it,
you should not have run time,
friends, in any center and the fourth one
says to attract these conditions for the entire time, friends, if I
click on confirm, friends, it will bring you to a new
interface, friends, here you
need your full date of birth, mobile number, email address, friends, it
is compulsory, after that you
enter the rule in option B, friends, let me
show you by clicking live here, like here we put the name,
friends, I will
not put my original here, that is what I am telling you here,
friends, do this and
enter the mobile number here, friends,
enter whatever is yours, I am
showing you here in the tutorial group
and here the email address, which should
come on your mobile number, friends, I
enter this investment here, friends,
you must be seeing here, the name of Navami is being
entered, friends,
enter the name here  The full name of 209 is
friends and here its mail address option will
come, if you want to enter then give it, if you do not want to enter,
you go to Hindi,
what is your relationship with him normally,
through whom you are entering, if you have a father then leave it as father,
you will have to click on continue here,
friends, in this continue will be caught,
your mobile number OTP will be asked,
you have to enter the OTP, you will get the OTP on the email ID,
friends, you have to enter it on the missing number,
friends, only after that you will be able to make the payment, so you can clear it through Paytm, whether Amazon or any UPI or any debit card net banking, friends, there is one more thing in this, friends, if you make a purchase now, then its
insurance certificate from friends will
come on your email Id, friends, and if you
log in to the back side of Flipkart application or deal with me, then
you can see it in that too,
friends, how did you like it,
please do tell us by commenting, there are mainly
four full in it, mostly airplane
and it is fine for those people, friends, the rest of
this is BCD, which are happy people, their  It
is fine for you but this old one, the
travel in it is cheap and the plan is the best, friends, I
hope that I will be
able to give you complete information in it at that time, if you liked the video then
like it, share it as much as possible
with your friends and family,
subscribe to the channel, press the notification bell so that
you will get the notification, we
upload such videos, friends, that's all
in this video, now I will meet you
in the next video, till then good